A Guide to the Virginia Dietetic Association Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(September 12, 1984), 1983-1984, TD(12) (Box-folder 013:022)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Photos from the Legislative Reception (September 20, 1984), 1983-1984, Photos(6) (Box-folder 013:023)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Photos from the Fitness Footwork 10k Run and 3k Run(October 14, 1984), 1983-1984, Photos(2) (Box-folder 013:024)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(October 30, 1984), 1983-1984, TD(10), AD(4) (Box-folder 013:025)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting (November 10, 1984), 1983-1984, TD(2) (Box-folder 013:026)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Lecture, "Improving Your Professional Image", 1983-1984, Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 013:027)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: National Nutrition Time, 1983-1984, Newspaper Articles (Box-folder 013:028)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Membership List, 1984-1985, TD(8) (Box-folder 013:029)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Newsletters, 1984-1985, Newsletters(4), TD(1) (Box-folder 013:030)
  Subscription Newsletter Notice
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(May 8, 1985), 1984-1985, TD(20) (Box-folder 013:031)
  Minutes
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Fifteenth Anniversary From 1970 To 1985(May 4, 1985), 1984-1985, pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 013:032)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(April 10, 1985), 1984-1985, TD(18), AD(7) (Box-folder 013:033)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Discussion, "Marketing Clinical Dietetics"(March 21, 1985), 1984-1985, Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 013:034)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(March 6, 1985), 1984-1985, TD(26), AD(4) (Box-folder 013:035)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(February 6, 1985), 1984-1985, TD(27), AD(5), TForm(2), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 013:036)
  Minutes, Reports, Letters, Recognized Dietetic Technician of the Year Award, Senate Bill No.628
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Letter in Support of Debra Mattes-Kulig, R.D.(January 15, 1985), 1984-1985, TD(2) (Box-folder 013:037)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(january 9, 1985), 1984-1985, TD(14), AD(7) (Box-folder 013:038)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Fifteenth Anniversary of NDVDA(December 12, 1984), 1984-1985, TD(21) (Box-folder 013:039)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(November 10, 1984), 1984-1985, TD(5) (Box-folder 013:040)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(August 14, 1985), 1984-1985, TD(17), AD(1) (Box-folder 013:041)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(September 11, 1985), 1984-1985, TD(20), AD(4) (Box-folder 013:042)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Lecture, Nutrition Quackery" by Stephen Barrett, M.D.(September 12, 1985), 1984-1985, Pamphlets(2) (Box-folder 013:043)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Business Meeting(November 13, 1985), 1984-1985, TD(2) (Box-folder 013:044)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Lecture,"Nutritional Support: Handling An Old Problem A New Way"(October 3, 1985), 1984-1985, TD(6) (Box-folder 013:045)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Executive Board 1982-1983, TD(18), TForm(6) (Box-folder 014:001)
  Membership List
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Secretary 1982-1983, TD(30), AD(2) (Box-folder 014:002)
  Minutes, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Financial 1982-1983, TD(41), AD(2) (Box-folder 014:003)
  Reports, Letters, Disbursement Request Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Meetings 1982-1983, TD(34) (Box-folder 014:004)
  Minutes, Meeting Records, Letters, Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: History 1982-1983, TD(1) (Box-folder 014:005)
  Letter
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Association of Allied Health Professions, 1982-1983, TD(110), AD(1), Newsletter(7), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 014:006)
  Minutes, Letters, Reports, Bylaws
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Public Relations, 1982-1983, TD(19), AD(1) (Box-folder 014:007)
  Letters, Flyers, Disbursement Request Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VaDA Lines, 1982-1983, TD(6) (Box-folder 014:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Bylaws, 1982-1983, TD(8), AD(2) (Box-folder 014:009)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Delegate, 1982-1983, TD(60), AD(3), Map(Photocopied:1) (Box-folder 014:010)
  Letters, Memoranda, Minutes, ADA Resolution Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Nominating Committee, 1982-1983, TD(17), AD(4), TForm(7) (Box-folder 014:011)
  Letters, Reports, Bollots
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Northern Virginia District, 1982-1983, TD(31), AD(1), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 014:012)
  Letters, Reports, List of Officers, Memorandum,
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Blue Ridge District, 1982-1983, TD(13), AD(1), Map(Photocopied:1), Registration Form (Box-folder 014:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Richmond District, 1982-1983, TD(20), Newsletters(3) (Box-folder 014:014)
  Reports, Letters, Questionaire
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Ronanoke District, 1982-1983, TD(5) (Box-folder 014:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Tidewater District, 1982-1983, TD(14), AD(1) (Box-folder 014:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Council on Practice, 1982-1983, TD(22), AD(1) (Box-folder 015:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Community Dietetics, 1982-1983, TD(25), pamphlets(2) (Box-folder 015:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Clinical Dietetics and Research, 1982-1983, TD(1) (Box-folder 015:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Consultants and Private Practice, 1982-1983, TD(14), AD(3), Name card(1), TForm(2), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 015:004)
  Reports, Letters, Seminar contents, "How to Consult" Schedule
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Educators, 1982-1983, TD(86), TForm(3), Newspaper Article(1) (Box-folder 015:005)
  Reports, Letters, Questionaire, Memoranda, Scholarship Rating sheet, News Release, RDYD Data Sheet, RYDY Guidelines
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Management, 1982-1983, TD(31) (Box-folder 015:006)
  Letters, Reports, Federal Register
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Legislation, 1982-1983, TD(25), TForm(1), Newsletters(21), Newspaper Clipping(1) (Box-folder 015:007)
  Letters, Workshop Program, Memorandum, Newsletter Order Form, ADA Membership List, ADA Legislative Newsletter
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Registration, 1982-1983, TD(24), TForm(9), Pamphlets(4) (Box-folder 015:008)
  Letters, Reports, Approval Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: By-laws, 1982-1983, TD(1) (Box-folder 015:009)
  Report
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Foundation, 1982-1983, TD(17), AD(2), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 015:010)
  Reports, Letters, Telephone Messages, Scholarship Recipients List, ADA Guideline
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Long Range Plan, 1982-1983, TD(13),Newsletters(2), Pamphlets(), Namecard(1), TForm(1) (Box-folder 015:011)
  Letters, Membership List
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Legislative Committee, 1982-1983, TD(28), AD(7) (Box-folder 015:012)
  Minutes, Surveys, Reports, Letters, Meeting Agendas
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Regulation, 1982-1983, TD(65), AD(3), Newsletter(1), Namecard(1) (Box-folder 015:013)
  Reports, Letters, Questionnaires and Comments, Memoranda, Senate Bill No/57
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Resources, 1982-1983, TD(4), AD(1), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 015:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VDA Legislation Information, 1982-1983, TD(26), Pamphlet(1), Newsletters(2), AMemo(1), Newspaper Clippings(Photocopy)(2) (Box-folder 015:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Correspondence, 1982-1983, TD(225), AD(12), pamphlet(1), TForm(11) (Box-folder 015:016)
  Letters, Reports, CVS, Survey Form, Speaker Suggestion Form, ADA Honorary Membership Candidate Form, Display Day Request Form, ADA Medallion Award Form, Nominating Committee Form, ADA Project Image Recommendation Form, Publication Announcement
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Miscellaneous, 1982-1983, TD(35), TForm() (Box-folder 015:017)
  Reports, Letters, Membership list, Elizabeth Lounds Memorial Lecture Application Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Executive Board, 1983-1984, TD(16) (Box-folder 016:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Secretary, 1983-1984, TD(18) (Box-folder 016:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Financial, 1983-1984, TD(68), AD(12) (Box-folder 016:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Delegates, 1983-1984, TD(42), TForm(2), AD(6), Pamphlet(2), Magazine Articles(2) (Box-folder 016:004)
  Reports, Letters, ADA Resolution Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Programs, 1983-1984, TD(11), Pamphlets(3), TForm(2) (Box-folder 016:005)
  Letters, Reports, Lecture Evaluation Form, Registration Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Bylaws, 1983-1984, TD(20), TPostcard(1) (Box-folder 016:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VaDA Lines, 1983-1984, TD(8) (Box-folder 016:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Public Relations, 1983-1984, TD(5), AD(2), Newspaper Clippings(2) (Box-folder 016:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Council on Practice, 1983-1984, TD(5) (Box-folder 016:009)
  Quarterly Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Consultation and Private Practice, 1983-1984, TD(4) (Box-folder 016:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Community Dietetics, 1983-1984, TD(8), TForm(52) (Box-folder 016:011)
  Reports, Poster Day Request Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Clinical Practice, 1983-1984, TD(4) (Box-folder 016:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Educators, 1983-1984, TD(9), TForm(3) (Box-folder 016:013)
  Reports, Letters, Survey Form, Scholarship Recipients List, Poster Day Request Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Career Guidance, 1983-1984, TD(1) (Box-folder 016:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Outstanding Dietitian Award, 1983-1984, TD(2) (Box-folder 016:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Scholarships and Awards, 1983-1984, TD(2) (Box-folder 016:016)
  Letter, Memorandum
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Management Practices, 1983-1984, TD(1) (Box-folder 016:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Legislation, 1983-1984, TD(3) (Box-folder 016:018)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Registration, 1983-1984, TD(7), AD(1), TForm(8), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 016:019)
  Letters, Reports, Prior Approval Forms for Continuing Education, Evaluation Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Nominating Committee, 1983-1984, TD(2), AD(3) (Box-folder 016:020)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Long Range Planning Committee, 1983-1984, TD(11) (Box-folder 016:021)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Blue Ridge District, 1983-1984, TD(4) (Box-folder 016:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Northern District, 1983-1984, TD(11), Newsletters(2) (Box-folder 016:023)
  Report, Letter
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Richmond Distict, 1983-1984, TD(10) (Box-folder 016:024)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Roanoke District, 1983-1984, TD(4) (Box-folder 016:025)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Tidewater District, 1983-1984, TD(5) (Box-folder 016:026)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Foundation, 1983-1984, TD(31), TForm(4) (Box-folder 016:027)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Correspondence, 1983-1984, TD(71), AD(7), TForm(1) (Box-folder 016:028)
  Letters, Reports, ADA TPP Chair Survey
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Special Committees, 1983-1984, TD(25), AD(1) (Box-folder 016:029)
  Letters, Reports, Survey Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Representatives to Associations, 1983-1984, TD(30), AD(36), Newsletters(5), Pamphlets(2), Form(3) (Box-folder 016:030)
  Reports, Letters, survey Form, Registration Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Executive Board, 1985, TD(24) (Box-folder 017:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Secretaty, 1985, TD(18), AD(2) (Box-folder 017:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Finance, 1985, TD(128), AD(305) (Box-folder 017:003)
  Reports, Letters, Minutes
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Delegates, 1985, TD(79), AD(1) (Box-folder 017:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Programs, 1985, TD(29), AD(1), Maps(2), Pamphlets(3), TForm(1) (Box-folder 017:005)
  Reports, Meeting Records, Letters, Registration Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: By-laws, 1985, TD(17) (Box-folder 017:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Public Relation, 1985, TD(46), AD(4), TForm(4), Newsletters(3) (Box-folder 017:007)
  Reports, Letters, Meeting Records, Ambassador Review
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Council on Practice, 1985, TD(2) (Box-folder 017:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Consultation and Private Practice, 1985, TD(5) (Box-folder 017:009)
  Reports, Registration Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Community Dietetics, 1985, TD(4) (Box-folder 017:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Clinical Practice, 1985, TD(6) (Box-folder 017:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Educators, 1985, TD(23) (Box-folder 017:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Management Practices, 1985, TD(4) (Box-folder 017:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Outstanding Dietitian Award, 1985, TD(2) (Box-folder 017:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Scholarships and Awards, 1985, TD(14) (Box-folder 017:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Legislation, 1985, TD(38), Newsletters(12) (Box-folder 017:016)
  Letters, Reports, ADA Legislative Newsleters
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Licensure, 1985, TD(72), Pamphlet(1), Newsletters(1) (Box-folder 017:017)
  Letters, Reports, Licensure Bill
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Political Action Committee(P.A.C.), 1985, TD(5), AD(1), Donation Slip(1) (Box-folder 017:018)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Licensure - Fundraising (VDA Cookbook Project), 1985, TD(23) (Box-folder 017:019)
  Letters, Reports, Book Order Form, VDA membership mailing lists
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Registration, 1985, TD(6) (Box-folder 017:020)
  Letters, Reports, Continuing Education program Evaluation Agreement Form, Prior Approval Application Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Nominating Committee, 1985, TD(1), AD(1) (Box-folder 017:021)
  Letter, Offices Nominees
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Long Range Planning Committee, 1985, TD(3) (Box-folder 017:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Foundation, 1985, TD(21) (Box-folder 017:023)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Representatives to Associations, 1985, TD(26), AD(1), pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 017:024)
  Letters, Reports, Virginia Culinary Arts Exposition and Competition Pamphlet
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Special Committees, 1985, TD(29) (Box-folder 017:025)
  Letters, Reports, Third Party Reimbursement
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Blue Ridge District, 1985, TD(3) (Box-folder 017:026)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Northern District, 1985, TD(15), AD(1), Newsletters(5) (Box-folder 017:027)
  Reports, letter
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Richmond District, 1985, TD(7), Newsletters(1) (Box-folder 017:028)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Roanoke District, 1985, TD(5) (Box-folder 017:029)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Tidewater District, 1985, TD(20), AD(1), Pamphlets(2) (Box-folder 017:030)
  Reports, Annual Survey, ADA Membership Application Pamphlet, Annual Report Pamphlet
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Licensure, 1985-1986, TD(80), Newspaper Articles(4) (Box-folder 018:001)
  Reports, Letters, House Joint Resolution 150, Federal Register, Study Guide for the Registration Examination for Dietitians
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Fund Raising Licensure, 1985-1986, TD(39) (Box-folder 018:002)
  Reports, letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Political Action Committee (P.A.C.), 1985-1986, TD(1) (Box-folder 018:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Registration, 1985-1986, TD(40) (Box-folder 018:004)
  Reports, Application packet
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Long-Range Planning Committee, 1985-1986, TD(29) (Box-folder 018:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Foundation, 1985-1986, TD(133), AD(1), Newspaper Articles(13), pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 018:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Associations of Allied Health Professions, 1985-1986, TD(72), AD(2), Newsletters(3) (Box-folder 018:007)
  Reports, Letters, Bylaws, Samplet Brochure
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Executive Board, 1985-1986, TD(58) (Box-folder 018:008)
  Mailing list, Standing Rules, Letters, Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Secretary, 1985-1986, TD(15), AD(1) (Box-folder 018:009)
  Minutes, Memorandum, Map
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Finance, 1985-1986, TD(141), AD(5) (Box-folder 018:010)
  Reports, Minutes, Letters, Insurance Contract
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Delegates, 1985-1986, TD(32) (Box-folder 018:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Programs, 1985-1986, TD(40), AD(8), Pamphlets(1) (Box-folder 018:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Bylaws, 1985-1986, TD(7) (Box-folder 018:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Public Relations, 1985-1986, TD(11) (Box-folder 018:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Council on Practice, 1985-1986, TD(15), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 018:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Private Practice and Consultation, 1985-1986, TD(4) (Box-folder 018:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Community Nutrition, 1985-1986, TD(3) (Box-folder 018:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Clinical Dietetics and Research, 1985-1986, TD(1) (Box-folder 018:018)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Educators, 1985-1986, TD(21) (Box-folder 018:019)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Management Practices, 1985-1986, TD(1) (Box-folder 018:020)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Career Guidance, 1985-1986, TD(7), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 018:021)
  Reports, Exhibit Reservation Request Form, Application Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Distinguished Dietitian Award, 1985-1986, TD(2) (Box-folder 018:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Nominating Committee, 1985-1986, TD(13) (Box-folder 018:023)
  Reports, Letters, Ballot
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Legislation, 1985-1986, TD(24), Newsletters(2), Disimbursement Request Forms(2) (Box-folder 018:024)
  Reports, Letters, Registration Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA (American Dietetic Association), 1986, TD(95), Newspaper Articles(18), Pamphlet(3), Newspaper Articles(4) (Box-folder 019:001)
  Reports, Letters, Nominee Suggestion Forms, Nomination Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Correspondence, 1986, TD(64), AD(2) (Box-folder 019:002)
  Letters, Reports, New Curriculum Request Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Legislation, 1986, TD(14), Newsletters(5), Flyer(1) (Box-folder 019:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Tidewater Dietetic Association, 1986, TD(20) (Box-folder 019:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Ronoake Dietetic Association, 1986, TD(12), AD(1) (Box-folder 019:005)
  Reports, Flyers, Memoranda
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Richmond Dietetic Association, 1986, TD(16) (Box-folder 019:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association, 1986, TD(12), Newsletters(4) (Box-folder 019:007)
  Reports, Letter, Mailing List
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Blue Ridge Dietetic Association, 1986, TD(5), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 019:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Special Committees, 1986, TD(5) (Box-folder 019:009)
  Reports, Memorandum
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: State Media Representatives, 1986, TD(20), Newsletters(2) (Box-folder 019:010)
  Reports, State Media Rep Questionnaire
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Council on Practice, 1986-1987, TD(50), AD(2) (Box-folder 020:001)
  Reports, Letters, Memoranda
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Consultation and Private Practice, 1986-1987, TD(8) (Box-folder 020:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Division of Education and Research, 1986-1987, TD(3) (Box-folder 020:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Management Practices, 1986-1987, TD(3) (Box-folder 020:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Delegates, 1986-1987, TD(109), Newsletters(3) (Box-folder 020:005)
  Reports, Letters, Journal Article, Resolution Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: State Talk, 1986-1987, Newsletters(3) (Box-folder 020:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Foundation, 1986-1987, TD(121), Newspaper articles(25), Pamphlets(1) (Box-folder 020:007)
  Reports, Letters, Flyers, Mailing list
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Silent Auction, 1986-1987, TD(8) (Box-folder 020:008)
  Letters, Memoranda
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Long Range Plan, 1986-1987, TD(36) (Box-folder 020:009)
  Questionaires, Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VaDA Lines, 1986-1987, TD(22), AD(1) (Box-folder 020:010)
  Reports, President's Message, Letters, Photocopy of Certificate of Recognition, Contact Agreement Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Distinguished Dietitian Award, 1986-1987, TD() (Box-folder 020:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Awards and Scholarship, 1986-1987, TD(43), AD(1), Newspaper Articles(4), pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 020:012)
  Reports, Memoranda, Letters, RYDY Data Sheets, CV